<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>shortcut on Xiaowei</title>
    <link>https://zhuxiaowei1998.github.io/tags/shortcut/</link>
    <description>Recent content in shortcut on Xiaowei</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zhuxiaowei1998.github.io/tags/shortcut/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chrome 常用快捷键总结</title>
      <link>https://zhuxiaowei1998.github.io/note/2021/12/20/chrome-shortcut/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhuxiaowei1998.github.io/note/2021/12/20/chrome-shortcut/</guid>
      <description> Reference to Chrome keyboard shortcuts
 Common chrome shortcuts    action shortcut     Open a new window Ctrl + n   Open a new window in Incognito mode Ctrl + Shift + n   Open a new tab, and jump to it Ctrl + t   Reopen previously closed tabs in the order that they were closed Ctrl + Shift + t   Jump to the next open tab Ctrl + Tab or Ctrl + PgDn   Jump to the previous open tab Ctrl + Shift + Tab or Ctrl + PgUp   Jump to a specific tab Ctrl + 1 through Ctrl + 8   Jump to the rightmost tab Ctrl + 9   Open your home page in the current tab Alt + Home   Open the previous page from your browsing history in the current tab Alt + Left arrow   Open the next page from your browsing history in the current tab Alt + Right arrow   Close the current tab Ctrl + w or Ctrl + F4   Close the current window Ctrl + Shift + w or Alt + F4   Minimize the current window Alt + Space then n   Maximize the current window Alt + Space then x   Quit Google Chrome Alt + f then x   Open the Chrome Task Manager Shift + Esc   Open the Bookmarks Manager Ctrl + Shift + o   Search from anywhere on the page Ctrl + k or Ctrl + e   Jump to the next match to your Find Bar search Ctrl + g   Jump to the previous match to your Find Bar search Ctrl + Shift + g   Open options to print the current page Ctrl + p   Reload the current page F5 or Ctrl + r   Save your current web page as a bookmark Ctrl + d   Save all open tabs as bookmarks in a new folder Ctrl + Shift + d   Turn full-screen mode on or off F11   Make everything on the page bigger Ctrl and +   Make everything on the page smaller Ctrl and -   Return everything on the page to default size Ctrl + 0   Go to the top of the page Home   Go to the bottom of the page End   Open the Home page in the current tab Alt + Home   Open a link in new background tab Ctrl + Click a link   Open a link, and jump to it Ctrl + Shift + Click a link   Open a link in a new window Shift + Click a link    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows10 常用快捷键总结</title>
      <link>https://zhuxiaowei1998.github.io/note/2021/12/20/win10-shortcut/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhuxiaowei1998.github.io/note/2021/12/20/win10-shortcut/</guid>
      <description>Reference to Windows Central
 Common Windows10 shortcuts    Keyboard shortcut Action     Ctrl + A Select all content.   Ctrl + C (or Ctrl + Insert) Copy selected items to clipboard.   Ctrl + X Cut selected items to clipboard.   Ctrl + V (or Shift + Insert)	Paste content from clipboard.   Ctrl + Z Undo an action, including undelete files (limited).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
